SAIFUR RAHMAN SAIF

M.E.R.N. STACK DEVELOPER



I am Saifur Rahman Saif, an engineering student. Doing my BSc. in Computer Science and Engineering from North South University. Proficient in M.E.R.N Stack. I have about 4/5 years of experience in graphics designing, motion graphics and photography. I am also well versed in UI/UX design (Figma). Currently working as a Full Stack Web Developer. Aspiring to becoming a better developer each day.

CONTACT

- 🙎 #177, North Vashantek , Dhaka
- 01738829050
- Mr.Saifnewaz@gmail.com
- Saifnewaz.me

REFERENCES

Md. Newaz Hossain

Contractor ,36 East Bengal Mobile : +8801715123925 Email : newazhossain6878@gmail.com

Md. Nasir Uddin

Manager Accessories ,H.R.M Sourcing Ltd

Mobile: +8801913135321 Email: accessories@hrmsourcing.net

SOCIAL









INTEREST

Photography , Working out, Designing

LANGUAGES

Bangla, English

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

EXPERTISE

React, Node, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Next.js, Vanilla Js, Material-Ui, Firebase, Html, Css, Sass

COMFORTABLE

C, C++, Java,

FAMILIAR

Python, C#

TOOLS

Git, VS Code, Chrome Dev Tools, Firefox Dev Tools, Netlify, Heroku

EDUCATION

2016 - Present

North South University

BSc. In Computer Science and Engineering

2006 - 2016

Adamjee Cantonment Public School & College

HSC & SSC

2003-2006

Peter Pan English Medium School

Preschool to 1st Standard

EXPERIENCE

2020 - Present RGB Jute

Web Developer

2020 - Present Upwork

Photographer

2016 - Present Freelance

Digital Artist
2018 - 2020 Brand Image Designer

RECENT PROJECTS

W Visit

WVisit

Www Visit

A Travelling Agency Website

- Tools: HTML, CSS, Flexbox,
- VS Code.

A Photography Website

 Tools: HTML, CSS, SASS, CSS Grid, Flexbox, VS Code.

A Dynamic To-do-List

 Tools: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, CSS Grid, Flexbox, VS Code.

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCES

UNICEF Bangladesh

Volunteer

2020 - Present IYS Deputy Country Coordinator

WSDA New Zealand